https://www.durhamcricket.co.uk/privacy-policy/

This website uses cookies (including tracking technologies) to improve user experience and provide appropriate information. If you continue on this website you will be providing your consent to our use of these. You can see our cookie policyand learn how to manage them here.
Close
Generated with Avocode.
Generated with Avocode.
Search
Menu
Search
TicketsFixtures & ResultsContact usNewsletter Signup
Match CentreNews & MediaPlayers & StaffMenu BackPlayers & StaffSeniorStaffAcademyWomenCricket BoardVitality BlastMenu BackVitality BlastVitality BlastFree All Stars Memberships infoWhat happens during Vitality Blast?Vitality Blast activitiesFosters FieldVitality Blast Refund PolicyMembershipFansMenu BackFansMembershipJunior MembershipProspects of PlayTravel ClubGraveney ClubHowzat LotteryRewards4CricketGround MapPlay CricketMenu BackPlay CricketAll Stars CricketDynamos CricketIn a ClubJunior CricketSenior CricketWomen's CricketFind a Cricket ClubSchoolsPrimary Schools ProgrammeChance to ShineSchool CompetitionsIn the CommunityIn CollegeEast Durham CollegeGateshead CollegeSunderland CollegeWomen and GirlsGirls’ CricketWomen’s CricketDisability CricketVisually Impaired CricketPhysical Disability and Learning Disability CricketDisability School and Community ProgrammeJunior League HandbookPerformanceLeague CompetitionsLeague-Based CoursesCoursesHoliday CampsSpecialist CoursesAbout Durham Cricket BoardBe InvolvedMenu BackBe InvolvedCoach CricketHow to become a CoachCoaching CoursesAlready a CoachJunior Cricket Format RecommendationsOfficialsCourses for UmpiresCourses for ScorersDurham Cricket ACOGroundstaffGroundstaff CoursesPitch AdvisorsGuidance DocumentsVolunteeringHow to VolunteerVolunteer Awards – OSCAsECB Coach AwardsClub SupportCOVID-19 Club SupportClub AffiliationClub FundingSafe Hands CoursesClubmarkOverseas Players at your ClubJunior LeagueAbout Durham Cricket BoardHospitalityMenu BackHospitalityCricketInternationalSeasonalConcertsEventsMenu BackEventsMeetings & ConferencesConcerts in 2021Parties & CelebrationsWeddingsProms & Leavers BallsConcert / Venue HireFoundationMenu BackFoundationAbout UsGetting InvolvedProjectsNewsPartnersCareersHow to find usAbout usMenu BackAbout usHow to find us360 Ground TourShopThe Sticky Wicket
Privacy Policy
GeneralWe, Durham Cricket , are committed to your (the visitor to our Website), rights of privacy and to responsible data management. This is why we have set out the privacy policy below.
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Statement by posting any changes on the Website. The new terms will be effective immediately from the time they are posted.
This privacy policy sets out the way in which any personal information you provide to us is used and securely stored by Durham Cricket. It applies whenever we collect your personal data (including when you use our website or other digital platforms), so please read it carefully.
If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy please do not use the Website or otherwise provide us with your personal information.
About usDurham Cricket is part of Durham CIC. This website and privacy policy applies to all entities within the Durham CIC including Durham Cricket, Durham Cricket Foundation, Durham Cricket  Board and Riverside Events.
About this privacy policyThis privacy policy explains what information we may collect about you, how we may use it, and the steps we take to ensure that it is kept secure. We also explain your rights in respect of your personal data.
Please note that our website and other digital platforms may contain links to third party websites and digital platforms which are provided for your convenience. We are only responsible for the privacy practices and security of our own digital platforms. We recommend that you check the privacy and security policies and procedures of each and every other website and digital platform that you visit.
How to contact us about your personal data or this privacy policyIf you have any questions about this privacy policy or about your personal data, please email us at marcoms@durhamcricket.co.uk or write to us at the following address:
Data Protection Officer Durham Cricket; Emirates Riverside; Chester-le-Street; DH3 3QR
The information we collectThe information we collect includes:
Personal information that you provide to us such as your name, address, telephone numbers, date of birth, payment card number and details, billing address, email address and details of purchasing preferences, which we use in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We may also record details of any disability or health needs you may have at the time of booking an event or service which will take place at the stadium or any of our other premises to help to ensure your comfort and safety. This information is collected when you engage with us through purchasing tickets or merchandise, enter competitions, sign up for newsletters or request marketing information from us. We may also supplement the Information that you provide with other information that you provide through your interactions with us or which we receive from other organisations, such as our sponsors and partners, and use this combined information.
Website information – our website and our social media sites utilise cookies or similar technologies, along with web server logs, to collect information about how the website and social media sites are used, and information about users.
When you interact with our digital platforms, we may also automatically collect the following information about your visit. This is primarily to help us better understand how our fans use our digital platforms to enable us create better content and more relevant communications:
how you have reached our digital platform and the internet protocol (IP) address you have used
your browser type, versions and plug-ins, and your operating system
your journey through our digital platform, including which links you click on and any searches you made, how long you stayed on a page, and other page interaction information
which videos you have watched and for how long
what content you like or share
which adverts you saw and responded to
which pop up or push messages you might have seen and responded to
your subscription status
information collected in any forms you complete
We may also infer your country of location from the IP address you have used to access our digital platforms and we may analyse which marketing activity led to you taking specific action on our digital platforms).
For more information on the cookies and similar technologies that we use and their purpose, please see our Cookies Policy here.
If you would like further details in respect of the information we collect and hold about you, please contact our Data Protection Officer whose details are set out above.
How we may use your dataAll personal information that we collect about you will be recorded, used, and protected by us in accordance with applicable data protection legislation and this privacy policy.
We may use your data for the following purposes:
for communication to you via mail, email, phone, mobile messaging or social media direct messaging
for record keeping purposes
to improve the quality of our service
for market research e.g. surveys
to measure and improve activity on our website and social media channels
in connection with targeting/advertising activities
to understand your preferences so that we can improve the products or services we offer
We may share and pass your Personal Information (including details of your purchasing preferences) with the companies within our CIC or associated companies in which we have an interest including, without limitation, any of our joint venture organisations. For a list of our associated companies, please contact our Data Protection Officer whose contact details are listed above.
We want you to be the first to know about new signings, competitions, club news, ticket availability and offers from official sponsors and partners. If you haven’t already signed up to receive these exciting benefits please click here. You can unsubscribe by e-mailing marcoms@durhamcricket.co.uk, or by writing to us at the address above. Please note, if you don’t choose to receive this information, we will be unable to keep you informed of new services, products, events or special offers that may interest you and our ability to inform you of ticketing opportunities may be affected. An up-to-date list of our sponsors and partners is available by clicking here or by writing to us at the address above. If you express an interest in an offer from one of our sponsors or partners, they may let us know.
We may also participate in Facebook’s ‘Custom Audience’ service from time to time. This service enables Dricket to display to you personalised advertisements when you visit Facebook’s social media platforms. It works by converting your email address to a unique number that Facebook uses to match to unique numbers that Facebook generates from email addresses of its users. Where we use Facebook Custom Audiences, we will only include you if you have consented to receive marketing from us. If you have given us your consent, you can change your mind at any time by unsubscribing or by adjusting your preferences in the preference centre.
Disclosure of your informationIn order to provide our products and services to you or to otherwise fulfil contractual arrangements that we have with you, we may need to appoint other organisations to carry out some of the data processing activities on our behalf. These may include, for example, payment processing organisations, delivery organisations, fraud prevention and screening and credit risk management companies, and mailing houses.
We may share your data with advertising networks and/or social media platforms for the purposes of selecting and serving relevant adverts to you via those networks/platforms, and to search engine and analytics providers.
We may share your data with third parties (a) if we are under a legal or regulatory duty to do so, (b) if it is necessary to do so to enforce our terms of use, terms and conditions of sale or other contractual rights, (c) to lawfully assist the police or security services with the prevention and detection of crime or terrorist activity, (d) where such disclosure is necessary to protect the safety or security of any persons, and/or (e) otherwise as permitted under applicable law.
We may share your data with our carefully selected partners (as may change from time to time) but we will only do this if you have consented to receive marketing relating to our sponsors and partners or if one of the conditions in the paragraph above applies.
Some of the organisations to which we may disclose your personal information are situated outside of the United Kingdom and European Union in countries which may not have laws that protect privacy rights as extensively as in the United Kingdom. If we do transfer your personal information to other territories, we will take proper steps to ensure that your information is protected in accordance with this privacy policy.
In all instances where we disclose your information to third parties, we will ensure that your information is appropriately protected.
Data Retention Period
Personal data will only be retained whilst we have a legitimate business interest in doing so. Following this period the data will be deleted from our system.
CookiesIn common with many other website operators, we use standard technology called ‘cookies’ on our website. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive and they are used to record how you navigate this website on each visit.
For further, more detailed information on how we use cookies, please refer to our Cookie Policy which you can read here.
Security of informationWe take the security of your information seriously. When you submit your credit card details to us, we use industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology to guard your information. In addition, we have security procedures in place to protect our paper-based systems and computerised databases from loss and misuse, and only allow access to them when it is absolutely necessary to do so, and then under strict guidelines as to what use may be made of the personal information contained within them.
Where a password is required to access certain areas of our digital platforms, you are responsible for keeping your password secure and confidential. Please do not share or disclose your password to any other person.
MonitoringWe may monitor or record telephone calls for security purposes and to improve the quality of services that we provide to you.
Please note that for your safety and security, CCTV is in operation in all of our premises which are open to the public.
Policy on childrenWe realise that many children will visit our website, or interact with Durham Cricket via other routes, but insist that all persons under 16 consult with their parents or legal guardian before submitting any content or information to Durham Cricket. Parents or legal guardians should, in particular, supervise children when online and we recommend that parental control tools be put in place. Although anyone known to be under the age of 16 may participate in competitions and promotions, notification of a win or prize will be sent directly to the parent or legal guardian identified in the initial registration process. Any publication of a competition winner’s personal details for visitors known to be under 18 will require parental or legal guardian consent.
More about your information - your rightsYou may correct or update your personal information at any time by emailing us at marcoms@durhamcricket.co.uk or by changing your profile on our website. Please include your name, address, date of birth and email address when you contact us as this helps us to ensure that we accept amendments only from the correct person. We encourage you to promptly update your personal information if it changes.
We will securely retain your information for as long as is reasonably necessary and in accordance with applicable law. If you wish to submit a request that your data be deleted, please write to us at the above address. You have the right to receive a copy of the personal information that we hold about you. Please write to us at the address above if you wish to exercise this right.
If you have subscribed to receive marketing communications, you can unsubscribe by changing your emailing us at marcoms@durhamcricket.co.uk.
Rewards4CricketRewards4Cricket is our fantastic rewards and loyalty programme which is free for all our customers and members to join and use.  As a Rewards4Cricket member, you will be entitled to earn Rewards4Cricket points on tickets, memberships and packages purchased at Durham Cricket.  For more details, please click here.
New Members – if you choose to opt-in to Rewards4Cricket when you purchase a membership or an advanced ticket (online or by phone) with us, you will have an account created with the programme for free using the details (including name, address and email address) that you use on your account with us.  Please note that you will need to set a password separately with Rewards4Cricket.  Once you join the programme, the information relating to your transaction (including the number of memberships, tickets or packages purchased and the total price paid) will be processed by Rewards4Cricket for the purposes of applying points to your Rewards4Cricket account.  Please look out for your Rewards4Cricket welcome email so that you can activate your account and start saving towards your next purchase with us.
Existing Members – as an existing Rewards4Cricket member, following a membership or an advanced ticket purchase (online or by phone) with us, the information relating to your transaction (including the number of memberships, tickets or packages purchased, the total price paid and any Rewards4Cricket points redeemed as part of your transaction) will be processed by Rewards4Cricket for the purposes of applying points to, or removing points from, your Rewards4Cricket account.  Please make sure that your Durham Cricket customer number is linked to your Rewards4Cricket account.  If you have any questions about linking your accounts, please contact Rewards4Cricket at hello@rewards4cricket.com.
How Rewards4Cricket will use your information:
To provide member benefits – if you are a customer who is a member of the Rewards4Cricket programme, we will share with Rewards4Cricket information concerning your transactions with us.  The information we share will be used by Rewards4Cricket to provide you with member benefits and to operate the Rewards4Cricket programme.  For more information on how Rewards4Cricket will use your information please see its privacy notice, which can be viewed here.  Where we share your information in this way, we are not responsible for Rewards4Cricket or how it uses your information as a member of the Rewards4Cricket programme.
For further details about the Rewards4Cricket programme and/or to view Rewards4Cricket’s full terms and conditions, please click here.
Should you wish to opt-out of the Rewards4Cricket programme, you may do so at any time by contacting Rewards4Cricket by email at hello@rewards4cricket.com.
As a service provider to us – from time to time, we ask Rewards4Cricket to help us look at improvements to the way in which we engage with our customers.  This includes making recommendations to help customers save money on their ticket purchases, providing the tools to help us incentivise customers to come to one of our matchdays or improving their customer experience at Durham Cricket.  In providing these services, we may disclose transactional information to Rewards4Cricket about our customers (who may not be Rewards4Cricket members) so that Rewards4Cricket may analyse transactional information, customer purchases and behaviours (and trends) as well as segmenting our customer database.  For the purposes of performing these tasks, we continue to control any information shared – Rewards4Cricket acts under our instruction and as a data processor only and will not use your personal information for its own purposes.
Changes to this privacy policyWe aim to meet high standards and so our policies and procedures are constantly under review. From time to time we may change this privacy policy. Accordingly, we recommend that you check this page periodically in order to review the latest version.
Where to make a complaintIf you have a complaint regarding any aspect of your personal data or this privacy policy, please write to us at the above address. If you are still not satisfied with the outcome of your complaint, you may write to the Information Commissioner’s Office at the following address:
Information Commissioner’s Office:
Wycliffe House; Water Lane; Wilmslow; Cheshire; SK9 5AF
You can also contact the Information Commissioner’s Office using their online form: https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/email/
Last updated
24 September 2019
